God's undisputable and incontestable power is being demonstrated
as the morning water is ministered by the evangelists sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua in Jesus' name.
As satanic forces tremble at the mention of the name of Jesus Christ,
the demons confess their evil activities.
Watch and see what happened when light met darkness in the life of this woman.
Fire all over your body! Fire! Fire in the name of Jesus Christ!
Speak out! Who are you?
Ministration Of The Morning Water in Jesus' Name
Who are you?
Who are you in this body?
We are the marine goddess.
How many of you are inside this body?
We are two billion.
Ministration Of The Morning Water In Jesus' Name
Who else?
Python.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
So, you say you are python. Fire!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
What have you done to her, you demon?
I slept with the family and they used her to do a sacrifice.
We initiated her but that is the same girl who called on the Most High God.
What have you done to her career?
He wants to equip her with power and strength but we don't agree.
We came to fight her with two billion serpents.
How do you destroy them - her family?
I kill them like chicken!
You kill them like chicken?
Yes.
How? Explain. How do you operate?
I kill them. They have sinned against me, so I kill them.
How many of them have you killed?
Uncountable. She doesn't know her mother. I killed her father too.
You killed the mother and the father?
I killed all of the family; she doesn't know them.
She was running away from my kingdom.
Who are you that is killing them?
I am Korle.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
What have you done to her career?
She's very brilliant but we don't want her to succeed because of Divine strength and power.
Why don't you want her succeed?
Because she is our sacrificial lamb.
Sacrificial lamb?
Yes.
They have used her to atone for the sin committed by her great-great-grandparents.
They dedicated her to you?
Yes!
What else have you done to her?
We caused her to sleep with people, so that we can gain more people in our marine kingdom.
You cause her to sleep with people?
Yes.
How? Explain, you demon! How do you operate? How do you use her?
Be very careful with me! Do you understand?
Speak out! How do you use her?
We entered her and we entered the man too.
You entered her and the man too?
It's so that we can get the souls in our kingdom.
What else have you done to her?
We killed her but your master created another body within her.
You killed her?
Yes.
We cut her heart but your master sewed it.
We even bombed and shot her but she didn't die.
That's why we entered her with two billion snakes
so that we can tie her down before the two queens.
How long have you been in this body, you demon?
Since childhood.
She flies like a vulture, like an eagle.
You fly like an eagle?
Yes, because she's a warrior.
When you fly, what happens? What do you do?
We fight in the dark clouds; we are the agents of the dark clouds.
Look, when rain wanted to fall, it did not because the cloud was very dark.
We used someone to block the cloud but she stood and prayed and the barrier was broken.
Now, the rain is falling. The time has come but we have come to fight.
Ok. Right now it is time for you to go in the name of Jesus Christ.
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ! All over your body! In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus!
Your ring, your crown. Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ! Take your ring, your crown! All over your body! Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire! All over your body in the name of Jesus Christ, in the blood of Jesus Christ!
There's no hiding place for you demon! Fire!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ! All over your body! Fire! Your ring, your crown, your head!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ! Wherever that power is located! Fire!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ! Fire! There's no hiding place for you demon!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
All over your body! Your head! Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
There's no hiding place for you! Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
All over your body! Wherever that power is located! In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ! All over your body! Your head, your toes! Take your rings, your crown!
Fire! You python! You demon! Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Your ring, your crown! Take them off! In the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ! Out, in Jesus' name!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In Jesus' name! You are declared free in Jesus' name!
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Give thanks to God.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Indeed God is with us.
My name is Mary Penuku Nenyo. I come from Ghana - the Volta region.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was that I was in bondage - serious bondage.
Because of Christ, I was transferred from the kingdom of darkness to His marvellous light.
Mary (Deliverance Testimony)
My testimony goes like this.
My parents had their origin from Bakpa, Awaduwe.
They travelled to Ivory Coast and stayed there for fishing.
During that time, I was born to them.
Then, a message came to them one day that my family needed me
and that they should release me to them
to atone for the sin committed by my great-great-grandfather.
They told my family that there were serious deaths in the family because
my great-great-grandfather had sinned against the God, Korle,
which resulted in a curse in my family.
So, they said the gods had appointed me and that I was the only one they could send to him
to atone for the sin committed by my great-great-grandfather.
So, explain to us what it was you were told that your great-great-grandfather actually committed.
They said that my great-great-grandfather had slept with a 'Trokosi', an outcast.
My great-great-grandfather slept with an outcast, which resulted in a curse in the family.
In a week, up to ten or five people could die in my family.
They had gone to ask the oracle, Korle, and it said it was the one killing the people in my family.
So, it said it needed a maiden virgin girl - a baby girl for a sacrifice.
Because of fear, anxiety and trauma in the family, they took me from my mother
to go and atone for the sin.
It happened that my mother couldn't carry the burden. So, it was my father who brought me
to my hometown in Ghana.
Then, they bought hoes, cutlasses, clothes and beads like for someone who was getting married -
a bride.
They took me to Mamfi Ougame (Korle's shrine) for the atonement.
In an initiation rite, they took me to the riverside and initiated me on a journey of no return.
A journey of no return.
Then, public humiliation was organised - they needed to humiliate me in public.
So, I was humiliated - my clothes were stripped.
They tore them and my hair was shaved.
I was then introduced to an old priest as my husband together with other maidens.
So, you mean to say, sister, that as a very young girl ... just give us an idea of your age at this period
when you were taken and given as a sacrifice to this shrine.
I can't actually recollect my age but I was very young.
We had seniors. It was like a system.
So, they told me that I was one year old when they took me to the shrine.
This was how I was humiliated. I endured public humiliation.
They humiliate you.
The work we do in the Trokosi system:
We had seniors and I was a junior - very young. They gave me a name 'Mamavi'.
That means, 'Small Trokosi girl, small outcast'.
As my job, I had to kneel down and pray to the oracle,
"Let somebody sin so we can get more people in our kingdom".
I had to beg
because there were seniors, and they had to come so that another person would come after me
so that I too would become a senior.
In my case, I prayed in my language, 'Evineva lo', which means, 'Let somebody come'
because I was tired.
But, in my case, nobody was coming.
Another thing we also did - the priest would just point at you -
he could call us chicken, goat or cow because we were cows to him;
then, he would call us and sleep with us just like that.
You are talking as if there are many young ladies like yourself in that shrine.
Can you tell us how many people were in this slavery, in this shrine.
We were about 500 in that shrine where they kept me - Korle shrine.
There were other shrines but ours was the headquarters.
And all of these girls - you mean to say that a very elderly man, a priest, a chief priest
was actually sleeping with all these young ladies as a ritual.
Yes.
He would point at you, 'Goat, chicken, cow - line up!' And he would sleep with you.
On top of it, when he slept with you and you got pregnant and gave birth,
you had to take care of the child alone.
They wouldn't help you but the child belonged to them.
Another task given to us was to bring hoes and cutlasses to the shrine to farm
for the priests.
As a junior - they gathered all the 5,000, their hoes, cutlasses, and the farmland was very far -
I had to carry them for my seniors.
When we crossed the river, sometimes I would fall inside.
Nobody else was coming. They said I had brought another spirit to the shrine.
You were talking about the work you were doing in the shrine
as someone that had been dedicated to these gods right from the age of one years old.
You were also mentioning about preparing charms for people. Can you explain more about this.
In the system, people would come.
Since I had not attained my puberty rights,
I was the one - being a junior - to prepare charms for people.
Armed robbers would come. I would prepare charms for them so that when they got shot,
they would not die, and even if they got cut, it would not penetrate.
My assignment was to prepare charms.
The more charms I prepared, the more evil spirits entered me.
When the priest finally died, I was accused of bringing a different spirit; that I was an evil child.
I didn't say anything.
When the priest died, I was very young
but since he was my husband, I had to perform widowhood rites.
The widowhood rites continued. They had to shave my head.
I was confined to a room and had to stay there for six days without water and food.
On the third day, I could not continue with the hunger and thirst, and I collapsed.
But with God on my side, I revived. I continued the rituals.
After six months, they cleansed us from the widowhood rites.
Then, life continued like that and every day, we were performing our duties.
I was very stubborn. I would move around.
They had warned us not to go out and that if they caught anyone going out,
the person would be severly punished.
But for me, that wouldn't enter my head because I needed food to eat.
I needed food at all costs.
I would sneak out to go to churches and other places to hide.
Sometimes other children would be following me, 'Hey, Mamavi!'
because they had never seen such before - we were naked.
I didn't mind them because I needed food.
One time, I went out as usual to ask for food from people.
Some tourists came to one of the villages to snap photos.
They saw me, and it was strange to them. So they told me to stop.
In the shrine, they had warned us not to talk about it,
saying that if we would ever talk about it, our families would be destroyed and we would die.
I would tell them that I didn't want that but behind their back I would say, 'Let it happen'
because I didn't like this kind of lifestyle.
The tourists met me and snapped this photograph of me.
They asked me why I was in that condition, and I explained everything to them.
Six months later, they came back again and negotiated with the shrine owners
saying that their system was very barbaric and inhumane.
They told them that they had captured young girls and kept them just to use them,
which was not good.
They came to an agreement to liberate us. They paid a huge amount -
six million Cedis (Ghanaian currency) and a cow.
The foreigners were able to pay the money and the cow.
At first, they didn't agree to collect the amount because they asked whether the cow was for them to sleep with.
Later, they agreed and finally, they liberated us.
So, just to understand what you are saying, sister.
One time when you had actually escaped from the shrine, looking for food,
you met some foreigners who were tourists
who actually took a picture of you, and you explained the circumstances that you were in.
Several months later, the same foreigners actually came with another organisation
and actually bargained with the head of that shrine
and agreed to an exchange of money and also some other items
to release yourself and the other girls that were in captivity in that shrine.
Now, how old were you at this point?
I was eight years old.
So, you have been in that shrine your whole life.
As long as you can remember, you were living and brought up in that shrine?
Yes.
And you mean to say that the picture we are seeing here,
was the picture that was taken by these foreign tourists who met you in that condition?
Yes.
Ok.
After our liberation, the liberation brought about another problem.
I didn't know where to go to because I couldn't remember my village or where I came from.
So, there was an elderly woman, an inmate, who took interest in me and took care of me.
She was the one who told me the story about myself, which I told earlier.
She said she knew where I came from - an island called Awaduwe.
She showed me where I was from, and I traced my family house.
When I went there, they told me I couldn't enter.
They said if I entered the house, I may bring the curse back to them.
So, I was banished again from my family.
I had nowhere to go to. So, I had to return back to the shrine, to stay there alone.
So, at the age of eight, you actually found where your family was living
but they banished and rejected you again.
Yes, they rejected me, saying that if they welcomed me back to the family,
I might bring the curse back to them.
They had actually used me as a sacrifice. So, if they welcomed me,
So, I was driven out of the town.
So, I went back. I had nowhere else to go to.
I went back to stay in the shrine alone.
Life continued there.
I had to fend for myself.
I would go and pluck mangoes.
When people burned their charcoals, I would go and pick some and sell
in order to take care of myself.
I stayed alone for about three years.
One day when I was selling, an NGO, 'International Needs Organisation', saw me.
They told me, "Mamavi, we have liberated you. Why are you still here?"
Then I told her the other side of my story.
After our liberation, they gave training to the older ones.
While others were given money to settle down with.
Some were trained to do handicraft.
As for me, being at that tender age and my family didn't even want me -
if you gave them that kind of money, they may collect it but they wouldn't take care of me.
I said they should keep the money and use it to take care of me
and help me to go to school to the level I wanted.
When I was in the shrine, I loved school because I saw how school children dressed up nicely
to go to school.
I liked it. So, when they went to school like that, I would go and hide under the teacher's table
so that I could learn because if the other children saw me, they would be hooting at me,
calling me 'Mamavi' because of the way I dressed.
So, I would hide under the teacher's table, and the teacher liked me.
I would go under to see what they were writing.
I would also draw a line and write, 'A B C 1 2 3'.
That time, I knew how to spell, 'Standing, sitting, eating, pulling, pushing' and all that.
So, you mean to say, sister, that you were brought up not wearing any clothes.
You were brought up living naked, moving around naked. That is how you were actually brought up?
Yes.
The foreigners took me and said that since I had chosen education, they would educate me.
They handed me over to some people who paid my school fees,
bought books and other things for me.
God saw me through, and I was able to complete Senior Seconary School
with the help of I.N. (NGO).
After my education, problems and challenges started
between the woman I was staying with and I.N. (NGO).
The woman kicked me out. So, I had to go.
After I was kicked out of the village, I was introduced to an old relative in Aflao (Ghana).
Since I had been kicked out, I had to go there and stay with her.
That was like going from the frying pan to fire.
That was when the suffering started.
But before you go ahead, sister, just to understand what you are saying.
Even though you had physically left this shrine and people were trying to help you
go through education, because those evil spirits were still inside of you,
it was still pushing you to live a life of slavery. To the point of wherever you went,
you were experiencing that extreme suffering. Is that right?
Yes.
I experienced rejection.
In my life, I stayed with 11 people and experienced a series of rejections.
They would sack me, "Go away", and I wouldn't know what to do.
I stayed with 11 people and experience maltreatment and abuse.
So, I went back.
The spirits still came to me.
When I went to Aflao, I had a dream that cars were destroyed
and raptures had taken place.
Cars and buildings were being destroyed. People were flying but I could not fly.
Then, I saw the Saviour, the Most High God, Jesus Christ.
So, what we understand from what our sister is saying,
she has really passed through many terrible, horrific life experiences
before her final coming to The SCOAN.
And you were explaining, sister, that those spirits continued to attack you.
Could you explain to us, just briefly, how those attacks would happen
and how that would affect you and your behaviour.
I talked about abuses - sexual abuse.
Any man I met always wanted to sleep with me.
Even if I told them my story, they would want to sleep with me.
The demons would enter the men and make them sleep with me.
When they would finish sleeping with me, they would tell me, "Go, I don't need you any longer"
and I would go.
I met a man who said the international NGO was not taking care of me properly.
He said he loved me and I too said I loved him. He said he wanted to help and marry me.
After sleeping with me, he said, "Everybody has needs",
that if I thought my needs would be provided by him, I was joking. He drove me out.
When I went to Aflao, I had a dream where I saw Jesus Christ:
Cars and building were being destroyed; I saw people flying - they were going to Heaven.
But I could not fly.
Then, I asked Jesus why I couldn't fly; that was it because of my sin,
that I had sinned against Him and could not control myself?
Then, He told me that He would put something on me that would stop me from sinning.
Sister, we want to now talk about the area whereby you actually found yourself here at The SCOAN.
We know that journey starting a long time ago. Even when you had that revelation.
Even in the midst of this terrible attack.
But, because of time, we want to understand how you finally came to be in The SCOAN.
So, just explain that to us.
During my trials, when I was wounded and broken on 'my way to Damaskus',
I met a 'Good Samaritan', a woman. I told her my story.
After that dream, snakes were entering my body. I could see them.
They entered my veins, stomach. They were three pythons.
They entered inside of me. They were here (head). Another one passed here (right waist).
Another one passed here (left waist). Very big. Another one passed here (back).
Then, the small ones used to tie me.
So, I told the woman about it.
She said that the only person who could deliver me
from all those demons was Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That Good Samaritan, that woman helped me but it wasn't easy. It was very tough.
Sorry, sister. You mean to say that this Good Samaritan actually assisted you to come here to The SCOAN.
Is that right?
Yes.
She met you, and you explained your terrible situation.
She now advised you that God would use Prophet T.B. Joshua to deliver you,
and she assisted you to come here.
Now, by the grace of God, we know that last week you were here in The SCOAN.
Finally, God brought you here. Two weeks ago, you were here in The SCOAN.
Tell us your experience when you came to the Church and the Morning Water was ministered to you.
When we got here and the Morning Water was ministered, a giant man rose within me.
He was talking inside of me.
Suddenly, it felt as if someone punched me in my face, and I fell down.
When I got up, I thought the evangelist had punched me. So, I wanted to fight him.
I wanted to ask him why he had punched me.
But looking at the video before coming out today, I saw that nobody punched me -
it was a divine punch.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So, during that whole period of the deliverance, all you could recall
was as if a giant man was within you, fighting, speaking
and suddenly you experienced something hitting you.
And you fell to the ground. That was the power of God defeating those demonic forces
that had held you captive since your childhood. Is that right?
Yes.
Glory be to God! Ever since that incredible deliverance at The SCOAN,
just tell us the changes that you have witnessed in your life.
Before, I couldn't sleep at night.
I would have to move around because I couldn't stay in one place.
If I would sit down before, I would feel as if I was sitting on a snake
and if I wanted to sleep, I would feel as if I was lying on a snake. So, I almost ran mad.
I had already ran mad. But after that punch, all the snakes melted away.
Mary (Deliverance Testimony)
I was able to sleep like a baby.
Before, I never knew I was a normal human being.
I never saw myself as a normal human being.
But now, divinity has mixed with my humanity.
I am now a normal human being, in Jesus' name.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So, our sister really knows what she is talking about.
She has been under this bondage for her entire life.
And just since the deliverance, she has been walking and living in freedom.
Sister, how old are you right now?
I don't know my age, and I don't know my mother. I don't know her name,
I don't know my age. So, I can't tell you how old I am.
So, as you are talking now, you have no idea of the whereabouts of your parents,
or your extended family members? Because right from your childhood, as a baby,
you were separated from them.
No.
So, we can really understand what our sister has actually passed through
as a result of this evil spirit that entered her right from her childhood,
after she was used as a sacrifice to atone for the sins of her family.
We give glory to God that that curse was finally broken here at The SCOAN.
Sister, before moving ahead, we would like to ask you:
In the light of this experience, what do you want to advise our viewers all over the world?
Firstly, I would advise all viewers all over the world that the evil kingdom exists.
They want you to join them and the only way is - if you sin, you go to them.
They are also praying tirelessly for you to sin so that you will join them.
My advice is to stay away from sin.
Secondly, I have seen powers upon powers but there is a power beyond powers.
That is the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Mary (Deliverance Testimony)
The God of Prophet T.B. Joshua. Divinity that has residence in a human being.
The God of Prophet T.B. Joshua used Prophet T.B. Joshua to liberate me
from the kingdom of darkness to His glory.
Hallelujah!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Once again, we give all the glory to our Lord Jesus Christ.
He is the one that has liberated our sister, and it is a wonderful, very valuable lesson
that we can learn from her experience.
Physically, she was liberated from the shrine where she was living as a young girl.
She was taken out of that shrine physically
but spiritually, she was still under the torments of those evil spirits.
It was only here at The SCOAN where she finally received complete and total liberation
from her past through deliverance in the name of Jesus Christ.
Sister, we actually have a message for you from Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Upon hearing your story and what you have passed through,
Prophet T.B. Joshua actually used some people, made contact with some people in Ghana,
to try and locate your family home and where it is you are coming from.
You said earlier that you don't know your mother. Is that right?
Yes.
And you don't know your other family members?
No.
By the grace of God, through the arrangements and intervention of God's servant Prophet T.B. Joshua,
in the Church today, we have a lady...
Mary (Deliverance Testimony)
Testimony Time
She's going to come forward right now.
And she will be in the best position to explain who she is to our sister here.
Mary (Deliverance Testimony)
So, right now, we actually - before anything else - quickly want to hear a word from one of the ladies here.
She is one of the people that God actually used through Prophet T.B. Joshua
to bring the other family members that are here.
Sister, you are welcome. Can you introduce yourself to us and
also explain who you are to the sister that has just spoken and who the other people are that are standing here.
Good morning, Church!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I am Mrs Rebekah Emirenus, popularly known as Mama Becky.
I am from Ghana.
I am an evangelist in the Medina market. That was where I saw Mary.
She came to me one day and told me all the stories she has told us.
I told her that it was only Prophet T.B. Joshua who could deliver her
and that she should keep praying for me so that if I got money, I would sponsor her to Lagos.
That was exactly what I did two weeks ago.
I was very happy when I saw Mary being delivered.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So, this is the sister that actually met our sister in Ghana
and sponsored her journey here to The SCOAN two weeks ago,
after listening to what she had passed through.
Stating that she needed to seek the face of God here at The SCOAN for deliverance.
So, after her deliverance, sister, what happened? What happened next?
After the deliverance, on Tuesday, Mary called me and said that the Prophet had sent somebody
to tell me to locate her mother in the Volta region. That was my first time of boarding a boat.
I took the boat and went to look for her mother, Mama Happy.
Fortunatley, when I went, she was there.
There were some people who wanted to say no
but finally, the uncle in that house said she could come with us.
That was how I brought mama to Accra.
She stayed with me on Wednesday and Thursday and then on Friday, we set off to this place.
You mean to say that the lady standing here is the mother of Mary?
That is Mama Happy, Mary's mother.
Mama, that is Mary.
Mary & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
And the brother beside her: Who is he?
The brother is Kofi. Mary's brother.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Madam, you didn't know this family before then.
It was only through the deliverance of our sister that you were sent on this assignment
to locate her mother that she had not seen. Is that right?
Yes.
Wednesday was the first time I saw Mama Happy.
That is Mary's mother and Kofi.
At this point, we want to hear just a quick word from our mother here
and we believe she will be speaking a local dialect. So our sister will help to translate.
Madam, you are very welcome, in Jesus' name.
Can you introduce yourself to us?
Mrs Happy (Mary's Mother) - A Ghanaian living in Cote D'Ivoire
We want to ask our mother. What can she say about what she has just heard now
and does she have to say to our sister that is here?
Deliverance Testimony
Mary is my daughter. I have been looking for her for many years.
Mary is her daughter. She had been looking for her. She never knew that she would ever see Mary again.
Mama, you mean to say that our sister here, you have not seen her for how many years?
Mary & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
Since she was three years old.
When Mary was three years old, she saw her last. Since then, she has not seen Mary.
So, she is seeing her for the first time here at The SCOAN after her deliverance.
Mama, we know that most of what you need to say will not be said in public,
but what do you want to say to Mary right now as she is standing here?
What do you have to say to her upon listening to her confession and seeing what she has passed through?
What do you actually want to tell her?
Mary & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
I am very happy to see Mary again.
My daughter should forgive me. God should forgive her as she didn't do that intentionally.
She didn't know anything. It was the tradition that did that.
God should forgive her.
So, we have heard it from our mother here. She is actually asking God for forgiveness.
She said it was the tradition of her time that actually caused her to take that decision
to actually give her little daughter to the shrine and today for the very first time, she has seen her daughter
here in The SCOAN, after her deliverance two weeks ago.
Once, again, brethren, this is a very emotional moment.
It is difficult for the family here to comprehend exactly what has happened.
And we understand that not everything can be said and done publicly
but we are bringing this to your attention for you to know what Jesus Christ has done.
So, we can see our mother right now, begging her daughter for forgiveness after what has happened.
Mary & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
As Prophet T.B. Joshua says: Whether victims or perpetrators,
we all stand in helpless need of the Saviour's forgiveness.
I have forgiven her.
Mary & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
Hallelujah! Glory be to God Almighty!
That is the power of forgiveness.
As our sister rightly said that whether victim or perpetrator, we all stand
in helpless need of God's divine forgiveness.
Our mother here - upon hearing her confession - has realised her wrong.
She said she is asking God for forgiveness because it was traditional at that time
for her to take such an action
and she has seen the terrible repercussions in her daughter's life ever since.
We know that this is a reconciliation only God can bring about.
It is not possible ordinarily, if not for the intervention of God
who used his servant Prophet T.B. Joshua to actually locate Mary's mother
far away in Ghana and bring her here today to reconcile with her daughter
that she is seeing for the very first time in so many years.
One more time, people of God, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Finally, we are also seeing a young man here. We want to hear a quick word from him.
Brother, you are welcome.
I thank God for today is a big day for me.
God has used Prophet T.B. Joshua to unite the family.
I thank God for what He has done. God is our Saviour.
I give glory to the God of T.B. Joshua.
I thank God for everything. I thank God that He is the same yesterday, today and tomorrow.
I thank God because He used Prophet T.B. Joshua to bring us here today. I give all the glory to God.
Hallelujah! Let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We thank God for our sister's deliverance and what you have just seen now - the reconciliation.
We pray that God will give you the grace to maintain this deliverance
by making the Word of God the standard for your life.
And we know that upon hearing your confession, people of God are ready to come together
to support you to start a new life in Christ; now that you have finally liberated from the shekels of satan
and indeed, as Christians, the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
After her glorious testimony, reunion and reconciliation with her family,
Mary sat down to have a meal with her mother and brother
for the first time in so many years. Let's join them at this happy occasion.
Mary & Family Eating Together Enjoying Each Other's Company
We thank God for this great day in my life.
We also thank the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV and the whole congregation
for this great deliverance in my life.
It is actually a new day and a new beginning in Christ Jesus.
I also thank Mama Becky, my Good Samaritan, for such a role that she played in my life.
There is a wise saying that says that on the road to your divine destiny,
you need to meet the right people.
I think she is the right person.
This is the first time in my life I am meeting with my family, gathered and enjoying,
eating together at a table, and I am so happy and overjoyed.
I have forgiven her and forgiven everyone in my family, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Mary & Family Eating Together And Enjoying Each Other's Company
She is lost of words; she is singing to glorify God for bringing us together.
She is overjoyed. So, she is singing to glorify God for a great day.
Emmanuel!
I want to tell the viewers that there are many people like Mary, who are crying -
they don't have people to talk to.
If they come to you, show them the way.
The way is Jesus Christ and nothing else. Leave everything in the hands of God.
We really congratulate this family and thank God for what He has done
in the life of this family. We believe this is just the beginning of great things to happen
in this family. And the man of God, Sr. Prophet T.B. Joshua has sent us to the family -
the mother of Mary and also the brother
and our dear madam God used to bring Mary to The SCOAN.
The man of God has said that Mary is going to spend some more days in the presence of God.
After which, she will be joining the family again.
In the meantime, the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, has asked us to give the family
the sum of 100,000 Naira for their transport back to Ghana.
Mrs Happy, Mary's Mother Receiving A Cash Gift Of 100,000 Naira
from Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners
I thank you all.
God says, When you don't forgive your neighbour, He cannot forgive you.
I want my daughter to forgive me so that we will be at peace and live together.
I pray God will forgive me all my sins.
She is actually thanking the man of God for such a wonderful gift
that she has received from him.
Mary & Family Reconciled In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
The following Sunday, after sharing her life experience and being reunited with her biological mother,
Mary returned to The SCOAN to give thanks to God
for how her life had changed since her deliverance.
I was delivered from demonic slavery where I was sent to a shrine to serve an idol.
I continued living in slavery all my life from the age of one until I was delivered in The SCOAN.
I was delivered; I was liberated spiritually, materially and physically, as you can see now.
Mary (Deliverance Testimony)
I am here to thank the Lord Almighty for His kindness and favour,
upon my life, upon all the people and upon my family.
Last week Sunday, I was introduced to my family.
I was reunited with my family and my mother and that was the day I knew how old I was.
Now, I am thirty years old.
Mary (Deliverance Testimony)
It was really surprising to learn how old I was.
It is by the grace of God Almighty.
I want to take this opportunity, viewers all over the world and people sitting in this congregation,
to thank God Almighty and thank Prophet T.B. Joshua
for his love for humanity, the love that is radiating within his veins,
that I am enjoying today.
When I was delivered, he actually took care of me, clothed me and washed me
spiritually, physically, materially and financially.
People of God, Emmanuel!
Deliverance Testimony
I want to thank him.
I want to thank Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I want to thank you for your love that you have.
As God Almighty has radiated His power within you,
you have selflessly devoted yourself to God and were used to deliver me from demonic slavery.
I am free.
I am not a Trokosi.
I am not Osu.
I am not an outcast.
I am a bonafide citizen of God, co-king with Christ, co-heir with Christ.
I am born of God through Christ Jesus by faith.
1 John 5:4-5 says that whoever is born of God overcomes the world.
This is the victory that overcomes the world - our faith.
Who is it that overcomes the world but he who believes that Jesus is the Son of God.
I am an overcomer.
God Almighty gave birth to me through Christ Jesus by faith.
Deliverance Testimony
Emmanuel!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Deliverance Testimony
We are here this morning with a message from Prophet T.B. Joshua for our sister Mary.
We have listened to her experiences last week.
We know how she has been suffering in her entire life.
Even before coming to The SCOAN, she was under this very extreme demonic influence -
unable to have a job, unable to live like a normal person in society.
But we can all testify all today that she is free and we can see the glory of God shining in her life.
So, Prophet T.B. Joshua said that he wants to support you
to start a new life in Christ Jesus.
Amen.
On behalf of Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners worldwide,
we are here today to present to you the gift of 1,500 USD.
Mary (Deliverance Testimony)
Mary Receives 1,500 USD From T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners
The equivalent of over 600,000 Naira, which is for our sister to start a new life in Christ Jesus
now that she has been delivered from the kingdom of darkness.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
People all over the world and everyone here,
help me to thank the man of God and to thank God Almighty for such high amount to start life with.
He is indeed a man of love; a man of kindness;
a man that can offer such a huge gift to me.
I had gone to many churches for this deliverance but couldn't get it
but here, I was delivered and on top of it all, I was given such an amount to start life with.
Indeed, God is with us.
Mary Receives 1,500 USD From T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners
Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua. I am happy with your gift.
I will start a new life in Christ Jesus with the money you have given me.
I know that this amount with Christ and with your prayer and your fatherly love
and people all over the world who send their love and support,
I think life is a race in a tunnel.
I pray that at the end of the tunnel, when the Saviour comes,
we all will be caught up to the final ride with Christ.
Amen.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Once again, for those who may not have witnessed the experience of our sister,
or listened to the experience of our sister last week,
she said it was last week, here at The SCOAN, that she actually met and reconciled with her family -
particularly her mother - for the very first time.
We can see clips on the screen here that were taken after the service,
showing how mother and daughter sat down together and began relating and talking to each other.
Even feeding each other for the very first time in their lives.
Sister, just tell us what you can say about the reconciliation that happened here.
It was a great day for me because I was eating with my mother for the first time,
eating a sumptious meal for the first time without people giving me food,
sitting down with drinks and people around who love me.
It was just a wonderful day, a wonderful meal and a wonderful reconciliation in the Lord.
Thank you, Jesus. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Sister, we thank God for your life. We would like to ask you finally: What would be your word of advice
based on all that Jesus Christ has done for you and all that you passed through in life?
What do you really want to advise people of God and those present here?
I would advise people all over the world to stay away from sin
because the darker world is praying tirelessly that you should sin so that they can get your soul.
The advice is to stay away from sin and close to Christ. He is the only Way, the Truth and the Light.
The greatest sacrifice has been made 2,000 years ago.
That is the blood of Jesus Christ that was shed on Calvary, not human beings.
The greatest sacrifice has been made. So, make Christ your life partner, your will and your goal.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Once again, sister, we thank God for your life. We pray that God will give you the grace
to make His Word the standard for your life and we know that with the support of Prophet T.B. Joshua
and Emmanuel TV Partners worldwide - this wonderful gift you received right now -
better is not good enough, the best is yet to come!
We know you will be coming back with more wonderful testimonies to the glory of God Almighty!
Yes.
Wonderful testimonies.